Quotes don't have to be complicated we
make it simple for you to find low-cost
health insurance our matching system
sorts users according to their needs and
then connects them with the appropriate
insurance carriers for a good fit cost
as one of the most important factors in
your choice of health coverage
requesting quotes from several providers
at once as an effective way to ensure
that you don't overpay fill out our
questionnaire and receive your quotes
within minutes instead of spending hours
researching which insurers are
affordable and reliable we supply the
answers in a fraction of the time a
checklist for selecting a health
insurance plan buying health insurance
as a complicated process for many
reasons with so many options available
how you determine which one is right for
you which companies are reliable what
does a certain plan cover could you get
a better price to help your decision
making process we put together a
checklist of what to consider some
products such as pharmacy discount cards
seem like comprehensive coverage but
aren't actually insurance make sure you
are looking at plans offering
comprehensive coverage check agencies
such as Standard & Poor's or Moody's to
see how they rate an insurers ability to
pay claims the exact amount you'll need
to cover future medical costs as
unknowable because no one can predict
the future however do your best to
balance monthly costs with the amount of
protection a plan provides most likely a
cheap policy will not offer the same
coverage as a more expensive one and may
cost you more in the long run avoid
policies that lack a maximum
out-of-pocket limit on covered charges
confirm that the plan that you choose
covers the healthcare services and
medications you need if you want to keep
your current doctors make sure they are
included in the policies network if you
don't want to keep your doctors you
should still research to see if the in
network health care providers have a
good reputation and are located near you
once you select a plan examine the fine
print to check that your premiums won't
increase for 12 months
the number of health insurance scams has
increased as fraudsters take advantage
of confusion surrounding President
Obama's new health care legislation
because health coverage is so important
and expensive consumers should make sure
that they are truly getting the
protection they're paying for here is
our list of steps you can take to avoid
becoming a victim of a health insurance
scam look at the company's online BBB
reliability report these reports are
free to everyone and we'll show the
business's overall rating how many
complaints they have received and
whether the government has filed any
actions against them make sure the
company has a license with the state
insurance commissioner every state has a
department that oversees insurance
companies which must be licensed by them
differentiate between discount medical
cards and health insurance discount
medical cards can only be used for
reduced costs at certain doctors offices
and pharmacies they are not the same as
comprehensive coverage from health
insurers check to see that you are
buying insurance rather than a discount
card confirm that you are purchasing
health insurance with a trusted company
some fake insurers will use a name that
is similar to reliable brands read the
fine print it's a tedious task but you
need to do it do not accept any verbal
promises until you see them printed on
your forms check with your health care
providers and pharmacists to see if they
accept the plan you want allied coverage
as an online lead generator matching
consumers with businesses that offer
products and services of interest
you